I know you had a blending guy or something come in, Devil. The guy who made the coffee powder.
Oh, the guy from Shawky's.
You want to go for coffee?
Kichijoji, I think. He said this place.
Guatemala.
Loanda.
Yes, Loanda. Africa.
Wow. Costa Rica.
Well, I don't know... I run a coffee shop, but...
As you can imagine, on Fridays, there are people who come in to make purchases.
I can't stand up...
Do you mind?
When we don't have customers, we don't have customers.
Well, I guess you can just sit here.
Well, you're right.
Nowadays, they're trying to reform the way people work, and they're trying to treat their employees better.
What? Nothing is happening now? Nothing. Nothing?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what, what...
This is the Dharma doll. What do you think? I see. Well, well, well. Come in. Good evening. Welcome.
How are you doing? I'd like to send you a quick message. I have already received a summery letter.
Let's see, how about this one? How about this? It's a so-called "spider" cloud.
Not this cloud. This cloud, this cloud.
It's okay. You don't have to let it out.
Senpai, it's okay.
That's all I can find.
Here's a scorpion and here's a grasshopper.
Please stop. We've got enough. We have enough.
It's all right, isn't it?
No, no, no.
Well, well, some people eat bugs.
That's right.
That's the way of the world.
Is that all right?
Yes.
Thank you very much, Master Raier.
Good evening, Devil... the famous Dragon's Nest in Laputa, the castle in the sky... where that Laputa hides... is a big cloud like this...
I found something like it and I have a picture of it.
I love it!
It's not so bad... really...
May I?
Here we go.
That's it!
Oh!
Oh, moku moku.
There's a Raptor.
Raptor!
Rupta!
But I think it's really pronounced "rapta.
Oh, really?
So you were right.
Yeah, it's like...
No, no, no, no, no, no, someone said it to you.
No, but it's actually the real pronunciation.
I don't know what the real pronunciation is, but it's actually Rapta.
But it's not like you can say "Laputa" at all. The official version seems to be either one or the other.
It's hard to say "Laputa." Look at this.
You know what Dora said... "The Dragon's Nest.
I'll never forget it. I'll never forget it. It lasted three seconds.
You're getting shorter and shorter.
By the way, according to Mr. Pell, last year you didn't make a prototype in 5 minutes.
That's long! Any normal person can make a prototype in five minutes.
Five minutes is long. Three seconds is short.
Three minutes is like a cup of noodles.
Dora's leaving already. What?
How many seconds to start? How many seconds to start? Do you wanna do a line? Ten seconds!
Oh! I think 10 seconds is still not enough time for Pazuzu, don't you?
I was just thinking about the pants and...!
Ten seconds is very possible, isn't it? 10, 9, come on, we have to be quick! 8, 7, and so on.
But maybe Pazuzu doesn't have his pants on.
Oh, he doesn't even have his pants on? Where's Pazuzu? I don't know.
One minute!
If I had a minute, I'd have run by now.
It's 3, right? But...
40 seconds!
That's right!
40 seconds to build your own!
That's a little kind.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, 30 seconds.
Well, well, well.
But you know what?
I did an interview with Toshio Suzuki, the producer.
Toshio Suzuki, the producer.
That Dora-san?
Hayao Miyazaki's mother
Hayao Miyazaki's mother is the model.
You mentioned that, didn't you?
That Dora-san keeps popping into my head. I can't get her out of my mind. Why is she like this?
I'll write a search. You know, "Dora" is a pirate's mother, right? There was a person who was like a mother of a pirate leader, wasn't there?
What was it? This is Spirited Away.
That's her.
I know, I know. Was it 40 seconds?
She is kind, isn't she? You can count on her for whatever you need.
Yes, well, can I take one more summery picture?
This time, Osameko-san. A woman from Kofu City, Yamanashi Prefecture.
Komban Devil, everyone. Komban Devil.
It's been four months since you introduced me to a photo of you and me going strawberry picking, and this time we went to a park where we could play in the water.
M all the way.
So, is that okay? This is another summery photo, isn't it?
I love it! It's so dynamic!
I love it! Can't we play in the water like this when we grow up?
I can't. I don't know why. I don't know.
I don't know why... it's a little embarrassing.
I can't do it.
I don't get it.
I don't understand...
You're right.
You know, a little...
I tried to imagine it myself.
It's a little bit impossible.
I can't do it.
It's a little too much.
You've crossed the line.
That's right.
Well, it's not too late.
Oh, no.
What?
Too hard?
No way!
Is it bad already?
It was pretty refreshing.
Oh, no.
Do you have a water gun or something?
Can we just... just...
Can you stop... can you stop the play button?
Was that a video? Was it a video?
Maybe, but it was only Kuniyasu's, and he hasn't done it yet.
I mean, maybe... he's a high school tech student.
That's not fair.
But nowadays... there are boys all over Japan.
There are boys all over Japan, and if you divide them into two groups, those who can play in the water and those who can't, they're in the same category.
No, that's right, right?
No, I think they're different. Why?
You're not allowed to play in the water. You may play in the water, but...
But you shouldn't do it where people can see you. Men... well, maybe I'm one of them, and so are all the people around here.
Are you a yes-man? You've been judged "no".
Yes, even if they're young.
Is there another category? Like a special category?
There are people who are good at being young and people who are not.
Who's not young and who's not good enough?
It's like everything is bad.
Don't give me that. It's like a total failure.
Why can't there be a little something missing?
Something.
Like, the mustache barely stuck.
It's like it's not there.
Like it's partially connected to the skin of his neck.
I'm sure there's something like that.
Well, well, well.
I hope your kitty grows up to be a healthy kitty.
I hope you'll continue to send us pictures like this every season, since she's such a chubby little thing.
By all means.
So cute!
I want to tell you.
It makes me happy to see a child in motion.
It makes me feel at ease.
Yes, it does.
Yes.
I remember that time when I was with dirty adults.
I'm a little tired... like a master tired of being a master tired of being a master tired of being a master tired of being a master.
I'm like an extinct man... but it's not true.
I don't think so... it's embedded in me as something worse than it needs to be.
I'm sure that's true. They're educated.
Showa and 2022 aren't much different.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And you know what, I've always wanted to go to a soba restaurant in a train station.
You know those soba restaurants at train stations? I love them.
I love them.
Eki-Soba can be found all over Japan.
It's not easy to get there, but if it's far away...
If it's in my neighborhood, I can go there, but...
Those who have been there
And he even sent us a picture.
Mr. De Beer
Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture
Date Masamune
Sendai!
Yay!
Master Sarpon, Mr. Ebichu, Good evening, Nebiru.
Good evening, Nebiru.
I'm the same as you.
There are women who like ekisoba these days, too.
Eki-Soba lovers!
I love eki-noodles as much as you do, Master.
The other day...
I went to Aomori the other day and had some ekisoba.
It's called Toutetsu... Touzoku Kankou Railway.
The train line has been closed for a while now.
But the ekisoba was so popular, the store is still there.
What?
At the station...
The soba is still there?
That's right.
So...
What's it called?
The train line is closed.
The train line is closed, but the soba store was popular, so they kept it.
So...
I visited both the Misawa Station store and the Tochigi store.
I've always wanted to go there. It looks so good.
Look! Wow!
This is amazing!
I wonder if it's some kind of tempura.
It's soba with tempura!
It's fast, easy, and delicious!
It really is!
You can see the steam here too!
Looks delicious!
I don't know what it is, but...
I don't know if it's the material or what.
I don't know if it's the material or what, but it's kind of shiny.
Maybe it looks a little shiny.
Good food shines a lot, doesn't it?
I'd like to go there some other time.
This is a star of the ekisoba industry!
But Towada?
Where is Towada?
It's in Aomori, so there's a famous lake called Lake Towada.
So it's Aomori's star.
There's Aomori.
Like an axe.
Around here, I think.
Wait a minute.
It was really difficult.
There's the Shimokita Peninsula, isn't there?
Yes, yes, yes.
Hey...
Hachinohe, right?
I've been to Hachinohe.
When you go to Akita on the Shinkansen, it goes backwards from there.
Then you go straight and come back a little.
So the one that goes through Hachinohe goes to Akita...
Everyone splits up at Morioka, but usually Hayakusa and Komachi go to Akita and come back.
They go to Akita and come back. Wow!
He seems like a nice guy, doesn't he? Like they'll go once and come back.
What's wrong? No, no, no...
If he goes bad, I'll bring him back for nothing.
It's too unique.
It's just...
You're too much trouble. You've gone too far.
And, of course, there's Dr. Sapong.
I'm new in the ramen business.
I think we may have had a fateful encounter.
Let's start from the left.
The name of the restaurant...
It's called "Dame no Neighbor." I like it. He's a poet.
There's one in Shinjuku and another in Ningyocho. I went to the one in Ningyocho.
Next ramen... it says "ramen rice.
Yes, this way.
Bubba!
There's regular ramen and rice with beef sukiyaki.
And here's an egg...
You can use it as many times as you like.
I had it a while ago, so I don't know what it was, but...
I had it a while ago... so I don't know what it was... but it was a soy sauce ramen with ginger.
It's really delicious, and the rice is made in an earthenware pot, like a kamado.
I'd like you to tell us about it.
Is this an egg? A raw egg? It's a raw egg!
Is it chocolate spray? It's not chocolate spray, it's soy sauce.
This is? This is this. And this is chives?
Chives, chopped up? You can see the reddish stuff.
Is it spicy? It's a little spicy. Is it still spicy?
This is some kind of knock-knock salt and pepper.
What?
It's very stylish.
The restaurant has neon lights.
It's got neon lights and poured concrete.
It's a really nice place.
So the ramen shop has been getting more sophisticated lately.
It's getting more sophisticated.
There are really stylish places, right?
Like a bar.
It really is like a bar.
It's like a bar.
Live music?
Live music.
Jazz and stuff.
It was jazz.
What instrument is that?
Jazz.
What?
The trumpet.
It's a trumpet.
I think it's an ocarina.
Not the trumpet part, just this part. The trumpet part was short.
But, you know, I did some noodle popping here and there.
What kind of ramen do you like?
Shoyu tonkotsu (soy sauce and pork bone) is my favorite.
There's a lot of it on this floor. Soy sauce and pork bone.
I really want you to try it. But how did you find this place again?
How did you find this place again?
You know, on the old Twitter page, I had to say it like that... after I said it was an X.
I don't know... but it's all on the old Twitter page... so why not just use Twitter?
I don't know, I've already told you twice.
I've been watching X for a long time, and I saw a recommendation for a ramen shop that said something like "This ramen shop is really bad.
I was just in the area. I had to go there.
I went with Mona Lisa. She likes ramen, too.
She loves ramen. She's been looking for ramen at all kinds of places.
No, it was really good. It's good.
I recommend it.
I'm glad you liked it. Did I miss it?
I haven't eaten much lately. It doesn't help.
That's right.
What's wrong? I think you're a little overconcerned about the numbers. I mean, the doctor said I should check my eyes.
He said, "Where's the middle one?" I was like, "Oh, I've already gone as far as I can go.
You and the doctor are holding hands... and you're getting along so well... toward that glowing white light.
It's the last episode, isn't it? Like the last episode.
Peaceful. No, no, no, no, no... just... just... just wait and see.
I'll see how it goes... but I'd love to go... on the same day I ate there.
I've been working on the 9:00 a.m. research meeting, and of course I'm still working on it, but it's been getting a lot of rave reviews, and I think it's the ultimate form of the study.
It's like a weighing machine.
But as the ultimate form of this, we want to film on location in Fukuoka.
The home of Fukuoka.
Of course, it's in the famous Hakata area.
This is pretty windy.
There's more wind than you'd think.
It's right on my shoulder.
So to speak.
Of course, the famous restaurants in town are good, but...
But there are also some out of town places that are more residential.
Near Nishitetsu station or something.
It's like you're really good at ramen shops.
Hakata's really good.
I hear it's very good.
I'd love to hear about it.
I'd like you to tell us about it.
Let's go, on the show.
Let's go on the show.
We'll all hold hands on top of the doctor... and it'll be the last episode.
That's how the end rolls... the last episode... of the ramen shop ever.
That's cool, but I want to go all the way.
Let's go all the way!
How's everyone doing?
I don't know if it's your fault or not... but there's a lot of stuff here...
I've been trying to keep this company out of sight for a while now, but it's getting a little too messy
I'm inside, so I can go to Fukuoka like this, sending a blue breeze...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
That's why...
By the way, the live broadcast...
It's been a real cocoon this week, sir.
Wow, Juliana!
Tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch.
It's called a "whoo".
Don't you know it?
I'm sure my mom's in Cocoon.
I'm not sure if my mom in Cocoon knows it or not.
I don't know.
It was a time of bubble economy, when all the women with a fluffy sense of humor would go to the discos, and they'd play these parodies.
Have you ever seen a parody like this at a disco? It's like that.
I did this when I was in junior high. I was the leader of my elementary school cheerleading squad.
I was the head of the cheerleading squad. I was the bleep bleep, or 77 beats.
Wow, wow, wow.
Koukubun's pretty... active... active...
I miss the cheering squad.
Like "Yo, dahn", right? That's right.
Dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah.
Everything's fine.
You're falling down. There's something wrong.
The whole set is going sideways. The whole set is going sideways.
But you're all holding hands and sparkling in the light today, thank you very much.
Well, well, well, well. So, will you be back next week at the same time?
Next week we'll be live at 6:30 p.m.
6:30 p.m.
Boom! I know I said that twice, but it's important.
I've said it twice, but by all means... an hour and a half earlier.
I see... I see... I see...
Well, I'll see you all next week.
Thanks again.
I've received a lot of devil's charges.
Channel dismissed.
Thank you for your feedback on the tour.
Brian from Kokubun.
No, it's Leo Kokubun, you've been saying that for a while now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah... there's a big wind blowing right now.
Yes, yes...
I'm sorry to say that it's a little late in the season, but it's almost late in the summer.
It's almost late summer...
Why the charge? Why is there a charge coming, Devil Charge?
We're paying for ramen to celebrate the completion of the 15th anniversary spring tour. You can have ramen.
You'll eat ramen when we get in? Fujii-san will take us to ramen.
The principal likes him too. He's a dangerous guy.
He's one of us.
Momoshi-san, Momoshiki-san... 337 yen.
337 yen. - You're on your way.
Not bad. I'm looking at the sales tax.
Takeminchi-san, Master's soba locale scale, a big bowl of soba
Great, come to Aomori
You're all here... with your friends who love eki-no-Soba
In a microbus...
A tour
It's all wired up now
Can't go by train
You have to drive.
That's fine.
Yes, yes, yes, that's why.
Yes, that's what I meant. Thank you.
See you next week at 6:30 p.m. Then see you at 6:30 p.m.
I'll see you next week at 6:30 p.m. I'll see you at 6:30 p.m. I'm sending you third place?
You're only sending third place? Mr. Block?
I think this is probably number one. Number one?
6:00 p.m.?
10:00, my time, 30:00, yes.
Yes, I'll take that as a yes.
I think we have a pretty good idea, don't you guys? I don't think it's information, though, because you have to send that many signals to know.
Okay, so thank you all very much for watching this week.
Thank you very much.
I've been doing that all week.
Yes, I'm doing it all the time.